[
    {
        "question": "1. Choose the word that best describes the meaning of the underlined words 'In the match against the uplanders team, the sub mariners turned out to be the <u>dark horse</u>'", 
        "optionA": "played most brilliantly", 
        "optionB": "played below their usual form", 
        "optionC": "won unexpectedly",
        "optionD": "lost as expected",
        "answer": "won unexpectedly"
    },
    {
        "question": "2. In the question below choose the option nearest in meaning to the word(s) or phrase underlined 'Look at the <u>tell-tale</u> signs of battering on her'", 
        "optionA": "confirming looks", 
        "optionB": "suspicious marks", 
        "optionC": "revealing marks",
        "optionD": "signifying marks",
        "answer": "revealing marks" 
    },
    {
        "question": "3. In the question below choose the word(s) or phrase(s) which best fill(s) the gap: After Jerry had made the bed, he .... on it",
        "optionA": "layed",
        "optionB": "laid",
        "optionC": "lied",
        "optionD": "lay",
        "answer": "laid"
    },
    {
        "question": "4. Select the option that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence. Imona couldn't have attended lectures yesterday?",
        "optionA": "it was possible that Imona attended lectures yesterday",
        "optionB": "It was possible that Imona didn't attend lectures yesterday",
        "optionC": "It was possible that Imona attended lectures yesterday",
        "optionD": "It was impossible that Imona didn't attend lectures yesterday",
        "answer": "It was possible that Imona didn't attend lectures yesterday"
    },
    {
        "question": "5. Select the option that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence. If I left the country, I would arrange for my family to join me?",
        "optionA": "He left the country and his family joined him",
        "optionB": "In the event of his leaving the country, his family would join him",
        "optionC": "He did not leave the country and his family did not join him",
        "optionD": "He may not leave the country",
        "answer": "In the event of his leaving the country, his family would join him"
    },
    {
        "question": "6. Fill each of the gap with the appropriate option from the list following the the gap. That centre-forward was....... consequently the goal was not disallowed?",
        "optionA": "very well positioned",
        "optionB": "in an off-side position",
        "optionC": "a brilliant player",
        "optionD": "the captain of the team",
        "answer": "very well positioned"
    },
    {
        "question": "7. Identify the word that has the stress on the first syllable.",
        "optionA": "dismiss",
        "optionB": "intact",
        "optionC": "confuse",
        "optionD": "comment",
        "answer": "comment"
    },
    {
        "question": "8. Choose the option that best completes the gap(S). Is it true that Okoro ........ when the gates were closed?",
        "optionA": "had returned",
        "optionB": "could return",
        "optionC": "should return",
        "optionD": "would return",
        "answer": "had returned"
    },
    {
        "question": "9. Choose the the appropriate stress pattern from the options. The syllables are written in capital letters. 'Understandable'?",
        "optionA": "UnDERstandable",
        "optionB": "UnderstandABLE",
        "optionC": "UNderstandable",
        "optionD": "UnderSTANDable",
        "answer": "UNderstandable"
    },
    {
        "question": "10. Choose the option opposite in meaning to the underlined word(s). Her <u>ingenuous</u> smile drew our attention?",
        "optionA": "witty",
        "optionB": "naive",
        "optionC": "clever",
        "optionD": "arrogant",
        "answer": "arrogant"
    }
]

